斑点
Spots
六
Six
鱼
Fish
啊啊
Ah-ah
费加罗
Figaro
愿望
Wishes
斑点
Spots
以下是六名快乐谋杀犯
And now the six merry  murderesses of the Captain Hook County Jail
在虎克船长监狱里的
咒语牢房探戈表演
in their rendition of the Spell Block Tango
斑点
Spots
六
Six
鱼
Fish
啊啊
Ah-ah
费加罗
Figaro
愿望
Wishes
斑点
Spots
六
Six
鱼
Fish
啊啊
Ah-ah
费加罗
Figaro
愿望
Wishes
斑点
Sports
六
Six
Fish
鱼
啊啊
Ah-ah
Figaro
费加罗
愿望
Wishes
他自找的
He had it coming
他自作孽  不可活
He only had himself to be blame
如果你也在场
If you'd have been there
如果你目睹一切
if you'd seen it
我打赌你也会这么做
I bet you you would have done the same
斑点
Spots
六
Six
鱼
Fish
啊啊
Ah-ah
费加罗
Figaro
愿望
Wishes
斑点
Spots
六
Six
鱼
Fish
啊啊
Ah-ah
费加罗
Figaro
愿望
Wishes
有些人就是有些小习惯来让你失望
You know how people have these little habits that get you down
比如像贾斯珀和贺瑞斯
like Jasper and Horace
他们对衣料一无所知
they didn't know their fabrics
我要的是斑点纹
I asked for spots
不 不是条纹
No not stripes
也不是波点
not dots
是斑点
spots
有天我进了房子
So I came on this one day
非常生气
and I'm really irritated
我想要寻求一点点安慰
And I'm looking for a little bit sympathy
结果看见了贾斯珀和贺瑞斯
and there's Jasper and Horace
躺在沙发上喝着啤酒
lying on the couch drinking a beer
旁边还放着十码的波点布料
with ten yards of dotted fabric
不 不是斑点的
No not spots
是波点的
dots
我告诉他们你们敢再给我买成波点一次
So I said to them I said you buy me dots one more time
他们还真的又买了
and they did
于是我拿下挂在墙上的猎枪
So l took the shotgun off the wall
射了两枪警告枪
and I fired two warning shots
朝他们的脑袋
into their heads
他们自找的
They had it coming
他们自作孽 不可活
They only have themselves to blame
如果你也在场
If you have been there
如果你目赌了一切
if you'd seen it
你打赌你也会这么做
I bet you you would have done the same
斑点
Spots
六
Six
鱼
Fish
啊啊
Ah-ah
费加罗
Figaro
愿望
Wishes
斑点
Spots
六
Six
Fish
鱼
啊啊
Ah-ah
费加罗
Figaro
愿望
Wishes
我两年前在一个遥远的地方遇见了多克
I met Doc in a faraway land about two years ago
他说他是单身
He told me he was single
我们立马就坠入了爱河
and we hit it off right away
然后开始同居
So we started living together
他会去他的宝石矿上工作 回家唱  《嗨吼》
He'd go to work and little jewel mines and come home singing Heigh Ho
我会给他倒杯喝的
I'd fix him a drink
然后一起吃晚餐
we'd have dinner
后来我发现他跟我说的单身
and then I found out the single he told me
单身个玻璃
single my glass
他不仅已经结婚了
Not only was he married
而且有六个男朋友
Oh no he had six men
小矮人之一
One of those dwarfs
你知道吗
you know
那晚他下班后回家
So that night when he came home from work
我像往常一样给他准备了喝的
I fixed him a drink as usual
有些人就是等不及要喝手中的苹果汁
You know some guys just can't hold their apple juice
他自找的
He had it coming
他摘了一朵鲜花
He took a flower in its prime
然后利用它
And then he used it
摧残它
And he abused it
·
这是谋杀 但不是犯罪
It was a murder but not a crime
.
·
我站在大锅旁边
Now I'm standing over the cauldron
搅拌着为晚餐准备的鲶鱼
mixing up some catfish for dinner
做着我自己的事
minding my own business
艾瑞克王子突然冲了进来  带着愤怒的醋意
In stores Prince Eric in a jealous rage
他说 你一直在和川顿国王找麻烦
You've been screwin King Trenton he says
简直不可理喻
It was crazy
他一直大叫着 你一直在找川顿国王的麻烦
and he kept on screaming you've been screwing King Trenton
然后他就撞在了我的触手上
and then he ran into my tentacles
他在我的触手上撞了八次
He ran into my tentacles eight times
如果你也在场 如果你目睹了一切
If you'd been there, if you'd seen it
我打赌你也会这么做
I bet you you would have done the same
小飞象 唐老鸭 米妮 小小布鲁托
Dumbo, La Duck, Marcus Mouse, Pluto Junior,
阿米莉亚 阿基米德 芭贝特 虎莲公主 衣柜管家
Amelia Fieldmouse, Archimedes, Babette, Tiger Lily, Madame de la Grande Bouche,
汉弗来熊  德鲁希拉 来福 魔镜 班仔 高刚 弹跳苏
Humphrey the Bear, Drusilla, La LeFou, La Mirror, Banzai, Kronk, Slue-Foot Sue .
是的 但是你做的吗？
Yes, but did you do it?
啊啊 我无罪
Ah-ah, not guilty
我哥哥木法沙和我做了这个表演
My brother Mufasa and I had this exact
我的妻子沙拉碧总会跟着我们
And my lady Sarabi used to tag along with us
在我们的上一次表演中
Never the last number in our act
我们连续做了20个杂技表演
we did these 20 acrobatic tricks in a row
一二三四五 劈叉 雄鹰展翅 后空翻
One two three four five splits spread eagle back flips
一个接一个地空翻
flip flops one right after the other
在表演前的一个晚上
So this one night before the show
我去了费加罗酒店
I go down to the hotel Figaro
和土狼们喝了几杯
hanging with the hyenas having a few laps
他们没有斑马了
and they run out of zebra
所以我出门去弄几匹
So I ran out to get some
之后我回到巢穴里
and I come back into the den
看见沙拉碧和木法沙在做17式
and there's Sarabiand Mufasa doing number 17
雄鹰展翅
the spread eagle
我太震惊了
Well I was in such a state of shock
大脑一片空白
I completely blacked out
什么也不记得了
I don't remember a thing
之后我清醒过来 发现我在洗着爪子上的血
It wasn't untit later when i was washing the blood off my paws
我甚至还知道他们已经死了
Ieven knew they were dead
他们自找的
They had it coming
都是他们自作自受
They had it coming all the long
我没做
I didn't do it
他没做
He didn't do it
但如果我真的做了
But if I had done it
但如果他真的做了
But if he had done it
怎么能说我做错了呢
How could you tell me that I was wrong
他们自找的
They had it coming
都是他们自作自受
They had it coming all the long
我没做
I didn't do it
他没做
He didn't do it
但如果我真的做了
But if i had done it
怎么能说我做错了呢
How could you tell me that I was wrong
我对斯特凡国王的爱  深到旁人无法想象
I loved King Stefan more than you could possibly say
他是个充满艺术气息的人
He was an artistic guy
敏感 充满愿望
Sensitive and full of wishes
但他总是在寻找自我
But he was always trying to find himself
他每晚都会出去寻找自我
He'd go out every night looking for himself and on the way
于是他找到了弗罗拉 芳娜 还有梅里韦瑟
He found Flora Fauna and Merryweather
可以说我们分手是因为在艺术上的差异
I guess you could say we broke up because of artistic differences
他将自己视作鲜活
He saw himself as alive
我视他为死物
And I saw him dead
说不尽的下流事
The dirty bam bam bam bam bam bam
他们自找的
They had it coming
一切都是他们自作自受
They had it coming all the long
如果他们利用仇恨
Cause if they use it
我也可以利用仇恨
I may have use it
怎么能说我们错了呢
How could you tell us that we were wrong
他自找的
He had it coming
一切都是他自作孽 不可活
He only have himself to blame
如果你也在场
If you'd have been there
如果你目睹一切
if you'd seen it
我打赌你也会这样做
I bet you you would have done the same
再买一次
he does one more time
单身个玻璃
single my glass
他撞到了我的触手上
he ran into my tentacles
阿基米德
Archemides
17式
number 17
艺术差异
artistic differences
雄鹰展翅
the Spread eagle
斑点
Sports
六
Six
鱼
Fish
啊啊
Ah-ah
费加罗
Figaro
愿望
Wishes